# Jonathan Hodgson

Evansville, IN 47715

jonathan.e.hodgson@gmail.com - 6183132213

I am a dependable person with three years experience in security with confidence in what I do, becoming part of a team with professionalism in the job in both Us and foreign countries. I am able to adapt to changes still getting the final product to be safety and honesty.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# **Technical Operator**

AmeriQual Foods - Evansville, IN - October 2016 to Present

As a technical operator: ran machines, trained others how to run machines, ran different machines all over plant, fix problems that arise on the job with the machines, and do quality checks, and do paper work, and also instruct the line workers on their task

## **Equipment Technician**

Hydrochem LLC - Crossville, IL - April 2015 to October 2016

Responsibilities

Perform hydroblast duties, excute chemical cleaning or pipes and heat exchangers, and perform other task that invovle setting and breaking down the job. Travel to other states to go inside of power plants and do that job.

Accomplishments

I have been to a nuclear power plant.

#### **Bulk Tech**

Gruene Environmental - Austin, TX - 2014 to March 2015

Loading and unloading hazardous materials into tanker, cleaning up hazardous spills when required. Operate Forklift daily loading materials.

# **Combat Engineer**

US Forces - 2011 to 2014

Provide Freedom of movement for US Forces

- \* finding IEDs
- \* manning a gun for security
- \* driving to reach the destination
- \* provide aid to injured soldiers

#### Paint tech

Aerotek Inc - Princeton, IN - 2010 to 2011

Worked on primer line to fix defects in paint for the automobile to move to next process to finalize.

- \* sanding and looking for any defects to be corrected
- \* had time limit to finish work and if too much on that automobile pull line to stop it

## Reciever

TJ Maxx - Evansville, IN - 2009 to 2010

To break pallet to send certain items to different parts of warehouse

- \* break pallet and use hand jack to move it
- \* make labels for correct department
- \* wrap and sort on pallet to finalize order to finish truck

## **Material Loader**

Anchor Inc - Evansville, IN - 2007 to 2009

To load material to be cut for tent making

- \* fork lift skills to load and unload pallets to be stacked on racks
- \* inventory items for use
- \* hoist to load roll of material up

## **EDUCATION**

# **Associates in Applied Science in Electronics Technology**

Wabash Valley College - Mount Carmel, IL

## **SKILLS**

Maintenance, Computer Hardware, chemical cleaning

# MILITARY SERVICE

Service Country: US Branch: army Rank: Spc

August 2011 to November 2014

Combat engineer: drove heavy equipment, qualified on specific weapon, look for ieds on deployment, escort

others to a clear path, search individuals and vehicles

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

### Professional Skills:

CPR, Capable problem solver, Detail oriented, Microsoft Word, Microsoft PowerPoint, First aid, Microcomputer, Programmable logic controllers, Auto-Cad, Basic Welding, HAZWOPPER certified, Forklift Operator, RCRA training, and DOT training,